Wilfredo Palma Pérez

Computer Science Engineer, Analyst and Developer

Worker, active and capable. Engineering in Computer Science with more than 7 years of experience, knowledge of Information Technology and Communications. Desktop and web development, graphic design and translations. Currently I am programming and making web adaptations.





wilfre90dev@gmail.com



+53 58129882



Havana, Cuba



in linkedin.com/in/wilfredo-palma-328508b4

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

Wordpress Developer

Freelancer

2020 - Present

PHP, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Wordpress, Elementor, WP-Bakery

 Development of customized websites, modification of themes and plugins to the client's needs.

Design and development of VisualNet.cu VisualNet

2020

PHP, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, MariaDB, Apache, DNS, Windows Server, Active Directory

• Intranet website and, assembly of network equipment and servers.

Created, maintained, and monitored Company's IT network and website

"19 de Abril" Company

2018 - 2020

PHP, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, WordPress, MySQL

 Development of intranet website. Active Directory, LDAP, DNS, email, XMPP, VPN, Firewalls, ACLs, etc.

Creation of Warehouse's Computer System

National Center for Biopreparations

2017 - 2018

Desktop, C#, Entity Framework, SQL Server, Windows

• Software development to manage and tracking of all products inside Warehouse facilities, increasing the speed of processes

Implemented Production Information System

National Center for Biopreparations

Desktop, C#, Entity Framework, SQL Server, Windows

• Information management system for all production.

Developed BioCen company Web Intranet

National Center for Biopreparations

ASP.NET, C#, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL Server

• BioCen's main website, linking the company's accounting and production systems increasing comunications and data analysis.

EDUCATION

Engineer's degree

University of the Computer Sciences

09/2009 - 07/2014

Thesis

Havana, Cuba

• Computer System Reliability Assessment of Access Control in Information Systems

SKILLS

Web and Desktop Development Servers and Virtualization Self Motivated

ACHIEVEMENTS

EF Standard English Test Certificate (2020 - Present) https://www.efset.org/cert/taUCZV

Production Management Certificate (2018)

Polytechnic University of Havana "José Antonio Echeverría"

Active Inventory Management Certificate (2017)

Polytechnic University of Havana "José Antonio Echeverría"

LANGUAGES

Spanish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Computers Technology Design Videogames Family Music